LUCAS PADILHA

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Praceta Verderena 9, Barreiro
- +351 912 015 235
- lucas padilha@icloud.com

ABOUT (PROFESSIONAL) ME

I'm a person passionate for numbers, logical thinking and complex problems. All of my professional experience (in a lot of different fields) was based with this mindset and I'm pretty sure that kind of mind can change wherever environment that I am in.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Le Wagon - Lisbon (Portugal)

Full-stack web development | 2019

- Ruby on Rails
- Heroku
- C#
- CSS3
- Javascript
- SQL
- Heroku
- C#
- NET
- ASP.NET
- node.js

SQL ServerGit FlowBootstrap

- Git Flow - Bootstrap - GitHub - jQuery

FMU FISP - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

Civil Engineering | Feb 2012 . Jan 2015

- Numerical calculation
- Structural calculation
- Physics
- Mathematics

CNA - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

English Course | Jan 2009 - Dec 2011

LANGUAGES

Portuguese | ••••••••
English | •••••••

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Logistics and Warehouse's Manager

Brodheim Group | Jul 2017 - Oct 2019 (Portugal)

- Merchandise management
- Partial and general inventories
- Logistical control between chain stores
- Contacts with suppliers

Math and Physics teacher

Study Center Primavera | Jan 2017 - Jul 2017

- Explanations and classes, in mathematics and physics, for students from the 1st to the 12th grade.

Team Coordinator

Thousand Solutions | Mar 2016 - Jan 2017 (Portugal)

- Direct customer acquisition for energy business contracts
- Manage team for that same function
- Lead daily morning meetings

Salesperson and Sub-manager

Levi Strauss & CO | Jan 2014 - Dec 2015 (Brazil)

- Team management
- Sale of products to the public

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Co-founder of WALD project, a software that create and configure a Rails Application from scratch, just with the visual schema of databases.

In that project, I used JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 to build the public pages (404, 500), alerts, confirmations e buttons; bootstrap for default designs changing just the specific layouts with CSS; GitHub API for omniauth authentication; Heroku to deploy on a host service; and postgresql for all of our relational databases, Ruby on Rails for all the back-end, creating a default template, and using interpolation for each option choosed by the user.

Check us on:

□ waldproject.com